Christmas Solo is a romance, tv movie film directed by Christie Will Wolf.
Two single parents stumble into the possibility of love for Christmas, only to
discover that their daughters are embroiled in a nasty rivalry at school.
When the rivalry gets out of control, can hope and healing
lead everyone to a peaceful and merry Christmas?
Jennifer, played by Kelli Williams.
Nate, played by Jonathan Scarfe.
Charlotte, played by Pippa Mackie.
Melissa, played by Kayla Wallace.
Henry, played by Ricky He.
Audrey, played by Naika Toussaint.
Last Christmas is a 2019 Christmas romantic comedy film directed by Paul Feig and written by Bryony
Kimmings and Emma Thompson, who co-developed the story concept with her husband, Greg Wise.
Based on the 1984 song of the same name by Wham!, the film stars Emilia Clarke as a disillusioned Christmas store worker who forms a
relationship with a mysterious man (Henry Golding) and begins to fall for him; Thompson and Michelle Yeoh also star.
Last Christmas was theatrically released in the United States on 8 November 2019
and in the United Kingdom on 15 November 2019 by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the performances and chemistry
of Clarke and Golding, but criticised the screenplay and story.
The film grossed $123 million worldwide.
The tone is emotional.